http://www.placon.com/privacy-policy/

Placon Privacy Statement
Welcome to www.placon.com. This site is owned by Placon Corporation. This Privacy Policy is designed to tell you about our practices regarding collection, use and disclosure of information that you may provide via this site. Please be sure to read this entire Privacy Policy before using or submitting information to this site.
Your Consent
By using this site, you agree to the terms of the Privacy Policy. Whenever you submit information via this site, you consent to the collection, use and disclosure of that information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
About Children
This site is not intended for children under the age of 13. We will not knowingly collect personally identifiable information via this site from visitors in this age group. We encourage parents to talk to children about their use of the Internet and the information they disclose to Web sites.
Information You Provide
Some areas of this site may ask you to submit personally identifiable information in order for you to benefit from the specified features (such as newsletter subscriptions, order processing, resume/application submission). You will be informed what information is required and what information is optional.
Passive Information Collection
As you navigate through this site, certain anonymous information can be passively collected (that is gathered without your actively providing the information) using various technologies, such as cookies, Internet tags or web beacons, and navigational data collection (log files, server logs, click stream). Your internet browser automatically transmits to this site some of this anonymous information, such as the URL of the Web site you just came from and the Internet Protocol (IP) address and the browser version your computer is currently using. This site may also collect anonymous information from your computer through cookies and Internet tags or web beacons. You may set your browser to notify you when a cookie is sent or to refuse cookies altogether, but certain features of this site might not work without a cookie.
This site may use and combine such passively collected anonymous information to provide better service to site visitors, customize the site based on your preferences, compile and analyze statistics and trends and otherwise administer and improve the site for your use. Such information is not combined with personally identifiable information collected elsewhere on the site unless you have consented.
Use and Disclosure of Information
Except as otherwise stated, we may use information collected via this site to improve the content of our site, to customize the site to your preferences, to communicate information to you (if you have requested it), for our marketing and research purposes, and for any other purpose specified. In addition, we may make full use of all information acquired through this site that is not in personally identifiable form.
If you provide personally identifiable information to this site, we may combine such information with actively collected information unless we specify otherwise at the point of collection. We may disclose personally identifiable information you provide via this site to other Placon affiliates worldwide that agree to treat it in accordance with this Privacy Policy and use it for the same purposes. We also may disclose personally identifiable information you provide via this site to third parties that are not Placon affiliates, but only:
(i) in connection with the sale, assignment, or other transfer of the business of this site to which the information relates, in which case we will require any such buyer to agree to treat it in accordance with this Privacy Policy and use it for the same purposes; or
(ii) to respond to law enforcement requests or where required by applicable laws, court orders, or government regulations.
The collection, use, and disclosure of information contemplated in this Privacy Policy may involve a transfer of the information to jurisdictions located outside your country of residence that may not have equivalent laws and rules regarding personally identifiable information. In these cases, you will be asked to consent to such transfers and disclosures in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
Access, Correction and Deletion
To keep personally identifiable information that you provide via this site accurate, current, and completed, please contact us as specified below and we will take appropriate steps to update or correct such information in our possession, or to secure it.
This site takes reasonable steps to protect personally identifiable information as you transmit it to our site and to protect such information from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alternation, or destruction. You should keep in mind that no Internet transmission is ever completely secure or error-free. In particular, e-mail sent to or from this site may not be secure.
Links to Other Web Sites
This site may contain links or references to other Web sites to which this Privacy Policy does not apply. We encourage you to read the Privacy Policy of every Web site you visit.
How to Contact Us
If you have any questions, comments, requests, or concerns related to this Privacy Policy or the information practices of this site, or if you would like to opt out of future communications, please contact us as follows:
Placon Corporation
Attention: Information Systems
6096 McKee Road
Madison, WI 53719
608-271-5634
Visit our “Contact Us” section.
Changes to This Privacy Policy
If this Privacy Policy changes, the revised policy will be posted on this site. Please check back periodically, and especially before you provide any personally identifiable information. This Privacy was last updated on July 1, 2020.
ABOUT
About Us
Our Story
Sustainability
Innovation
Collaboration
Careers
© 2020 Placon. All Rights Reserved.
© 2020 Placon. All Rights Reserved.
